<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FoodyBuddy</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="text_cake">Cake is a form of sweet dessert that is typically baked. In their oldest forms, cakes were modifications of breads, but cakes now cover a wide range of preparations that can be simple or elaborate, and that share features with other desserts such as pastries, meringues, custards, and pies. Typical cake ingredients are flour, sugar, eggs, butter or oil or margarine, a liquid, and leavening agents, such as baking soda or baking powder. Common additional ingredients and flavourings include dried, candied, or fresh fruit, nuts, cocoa, and extracts such as vanilla, with numerous substitutions for the primary ingredients. Cakes can also be filled with fruit preserves, nuts or dessert sauces (like pastry cream), iced with buttercream or other icings, and decorated with marzipan, piped borders, or candied fruit.</string>
    <string name="cake_header">CAKE</string>
    <string name="pizza_header">PIZZA</string>
    <string name="drink_header">DRINK</string>
    <string name="text_pizza">Pizza (Italian: [ˈpittsa], Neapolitan: [ˈpittsə]) is a savory dish of Italian origin, consisting of a usually round, flattened base of leavened wheat-based dough topped with tomatoes, cheese, and various other ingredients (anchovies, olives, meat, etc.) baked at a high temperature, traditionally in a wood-fired oven.[1] In formal settings, like a restaurant, pizza is eaten with knife and fork, but in casual settings it is cut into wedges to be eaten while held in the hand. Small pizzas are sometimes called pizzettas. The term pizza was first recorded in the 10th century in a Latin manuscript from the Southern Italian town of Gaeta in Lazio, on the border with Campania.[2] Modern pizza was invented in Naples, and the dish and its variants have since become popular in many countries.[3] It has become one of the most popular foods in the world and a common fast food item in Europe and North America, available at pizzerias (restaurants specializing in pizza), restaurants offering Mediterranean cuisine, and via pizza delivery.[3][4] Many companies sell ready-baked frozen pizzas to be reheated in an ordinary home oven.</string>
    <string name="text_drink">A drink (or beverage) is a liquid intended for human consumption. In addition to their basic function of satisfying thirst, drinks play important roles in human culture. Common types of drinks include plain drinking water, milk, coffee, tea, hot chocolate, juice and soft drinks. In addition, alcoholic drinks such as wine, beer, and liquor, which contain the drug ethanol, have been part of human culture for more than 8,000 years. Non-alcoholic drinks often signify drinks that would normally contain alcohol, such as beer and wine, but are made with less than .5 percent alcohol by volume. The category includes drinks that have undergone an alcohol removal process such as non-alcoholic beers and de-alcoholized wines.</string>
</resources>
